(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-08-26T08:58:22.089605",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
生まれたてのドキドキを響かせよう
Let's make our newborn heartbeats resonate!
最高の時間 最高の仲間と
With the best time and the best friends!
キラメキに乗って☆
Riding on the sparkle☆
覚えてるかな最初の歌
Do you remember? Our very first song
あの日の声が震えていた
Back when my voice was trembling that day
あの日から続く未来は みんなと掴んだ今日だよ
The future continuing from that day is today, grasped together with everyone!
もっともっともっともっと 加速するハート
More, more, more, more, our accelerating hearts!
行くよどこまでも
Let's go anywhere!
準備はOK?
Are you ready?
ひらけ!夢のトビラを
Open the door to our dreams!
(123)
(1, 2, 3!)
キラメキライダー☆
Kirameki Rider☆
生まれたてのドキドキを響かせよう
Let's make our newborn heartbeats resonate!
最高の時間 最高の仲間と
With the best time and the best friends!
ここにいるよ 見つけてくれたから
I'm right here, because you found me!
君に会いたくてやってきたんだ みんなで歌おう
I came here wanting to see you, so let's sing together!
終わらないメロディ キラメキに乗って☆
An endless melody, riding on the sparkle☆
届いてるかな 私の声
Is my voice reaching you?
届けたいのは 君に笑顔
What I want to deliver is your smile!
理想の遠さに悔やしくて みんなで泣き笑ったね
Frustrated by the distance of our ideals, we cried and laughed together!
ぎゅっとぎゅっとぎゅっとぎゅっと 全て抱きしめて
Hugging everything tight, tight, tight, tight!
行こうどこまでも
Let's go anywhere!
準備はOK?
Is everyone ready?
すすめ希望の道を
Advance down the path of hope!
(123)
(1, 2, 3!)
キラメキライダー☆
Kirameki Rider☆
好きな気持ちカラフルに奏でたいんだ
I want to play my feelings colorfully!
最高の場所 最高のみんなと
In the best place, with the best everyone!
ここにいるよ 幻なんかじゃない
I'm right here, it's not an illusion!
君の心が幸せに染まるように
So that your heart is dyed with happiness,
重ねてくハーモニー キラメキ纏って☆
Wearing overlapping harmonies and sparkle☆
歌い続けたいな 踊り続けたいな
I want to keep singing, I want to keep dancing!
そんな願いわがままでもいいでしょ?
Such a selfish wish is fine, right?
だって楽しすぎてもう止まらない!
Because it's too fun to ever stop!
輝くステージで
On this shining stage!
嬉しい 楽しい 愛しい だけじゃ語れない
Happy, fun, and loving - words aren't enough to say.
今も 今も 悩みはあるけど
Even now, even now, I still have my worries,
ここにいるよ 私 ここに いるよ
I'm right here, I am right here,
君と同じ世界を 見つめていくよ
gazing at the same world as you.
きらめきライター 生まれたてのドキドキを響かせよう
Kirameki Rider! Let's make our newborn heartbeat echo,
最高の時間 最高の仲間と
in the best time, with the best friends!
ここにいるよ 見つけてくれたから
I'm right here, because you found me.
君に会いたくてやってきたんだ みんなで歌おう
I came here because I wanted to see you, let's sing together!
終わらないメロディ
An endless melody,
きらめきにのって きらめきまとって
riding the sparkle, draped in sparkle!
ありがとうございました！一曲目キラメキライダでした！
Thank you very much! The first song was Kirameki Rider!
改めてまして、これね、ホロライブ5期生オレンジ担当の桃鈴ねねです！
Once again, I'm Momosuzu Nene, orange representative of Hololive 5th Gen!
本日、お誕生日が！
Today is my birthday!
るいえーい！
Yay!
ぽちぽちぽちぽち…あっ緊張しすぎて最初間違えちゃったみんな
Tap tap tap... Ah, I was so nervous I messed up at the start, everyone!
どうしよう、汗やばい、脇汗びっしょり。
What should I do? I'm sweating so much, my armpits are soaked.
ねえ、見て見てこの背景！
Hey, look at this background!
え、どうどう、いつものさ、ライブ背景とちょっと違うでしょ？
How is it? It's a bit different from my usual live backgrounds, right?
これね、あの、猫の人手が作ってくれたから、ありがとう！
The Neko-no-hito made this for me, thank you so much!
放送終わったらね、あのリツイートするのでよかったら、あの作ってくれた人に見に行ってください。
After the broadcast finishes, I'll retweet it, so please go check out the person who made it!
え、めっちゃいいでしょ、かっこよくない？
Isn't it super nice? Doesn't it look cool?
あとこれ見て、猫もね、応援してる猫もご用意してみましたんで（笑）
Also look at this, I even prepared cheering Neko-no-hito as well (laughs).
てなわけで、今日は7回目のねねのライブ枠、お誕生日枠に来てくれてありがとうございます！
So, thank you everyone for coming to Nene's 7th live stream / birthday stream today!
はあー、緊張しすぎで無理、やばい、緊張する！
Haa, I'm too nervous, I can't take it, this is crazy, I'm so nervous!
すごいね、いろいろ準備して、今日はね、重大発表もあるから！
Amazing, I prepared all sorts of things, and today there's even a major announcement!
最後まで見てほしい、最後までみんな、いい？
I want you to watch till the end, everyone, okay?
今日はお願いだから、あの9時くらいまでね、時間ちょうだい！お願いお願いお願い！
Today I'm begging you, please give me your time until around 9! Please please please!
はい、というわけで、早速次は、2曲目にね、移っていきたいと思います。
Alright, with that said, let's move on right away to the second song.
さあ、今日はね、歌を歌いに来たんでね、みんなに歌聴いてもらうんだ、みんな聞いてね！
So today I came to sing songs, so everyone's going to listen to me sing, listen up everyone!
よろしく、じゃあさっきのステージに戻ろう。
Thanks, well then, let's go back to the stage from earlier.
考えたってわからないし
Even if I think it over, I don't understand,
青空の下君を待った
I waited for you under the blue sky.
風が吹いた正午 昼下がりを抜け出す想像
A windy noon, imagining escaping the afternoon.
ねえ これからどうなるんだろうね
Hey, what's going to happen from here?
進め方教わらないんだよ
We're never taught how to move forward.
君の目を見た 何も言えず僕は歩いた
I looked you in the eyes and walked off without a word.
考えたってわからないし
Even if I think it over, I don't understand,
青春なんてつまらないし
youth is just so dull.
辞めた筈のピアノ 机を弾く癖が抜けない
I can't break the habit of playing the desk like the piano I quit.
ねえ 将来何してるんだろうね
Hey, what'll I be doing in the future?
音楽はしてないといいな
It shouldn't be music, right?
困らないでよ
Don't even bother.
心の中に一本線を引いても どうしても消えなかった
Even if I drew a line in my heart, no matter what, it wouldn't disappear.
今更なんだから なあ、もう思い出すな
It's too late now, so hey, don't remind me anymore!
間違ってるんだよ わかってないよ
You've got it wrong, you just don't get it.
考えたってわからないし
Even if I think it over, I don't understand
青空の下、君を待った
Under the blue sky, I waited for you
風が吹いた正午、昼下がりを抜け出す想像
My imagination broke free of the afternoon on that breezy midday
ねぇ、これからどうなるんだろうね
Hey, what's going to happen from here?
進め方教わらないんだよ
We're never taught how to move forward
君の目を見た 何も言えず僕は歩いた
I looked you in the eyes and walked off, unable to say a word
考えたってわからないし 青春なんてつまらないし
Even if I think it over, I don't understand, youth is just so dull
辞めた筈のピアノ、机を弾く癖が抜けない
I can't break the habit of playing the piano on my desk
ねぇ、将来何してるんだろうって 音楽はしてないいいといいね
Hey, what'll I be doing in the future? It shouldn't be music, right?
困らないでよ あんたのせいだ
Don't even bother, it's none of your concern
心の中に一つ線を引いても どうしても消えなかった
Even if I draw a line in my heart, how come it wouldn't disappear?
今更なんだから なぁ、もう思い出すな
It's too late now, so look, don't remind me anymore
間違ってるんだよ わかってないよ
You've got it wrong, you just wouldn't get it
あんたも人間も 本当も愛も世界も苦しさも人生も
All you humans don't care about truth, love, the world, pain, or life
どうでもいいよ 正しいかどうか知りたいのだって防衛本能だ
Wanting to know right from wrong is just a self-preservation instinct
考えたんだ あんたのせいだ
I thought about it, it's your fault
考えたってわからないが 本当に年老いたくないんだ
Even if I think it over, I don't understand, but I truly don't want to grow any older
いつか死んだらって思うだけで胸が空っぽになるんだ
Just the thought of dying someday hollows my chest out
将来何してるんだろうって
What will I be doing in the future?
大人になったらわかったよ
When I grew up, I figured it out
何もしないさ
I won't be doing anything at all
幸せな顔した人が憎いのはどう割り切ったらいいんだ
The reason I hate people who put on happy faces, well, how do I put it?
満たされない頭の奥の化け物みたいな劣等感
I've got a monstrous inferiority complex festering in my mind
間違ってないよな なんかんだあんたも人間だ
There's no way I'm wrong, look, no matter how you look at it
愛も救いも優しさも根拠がないなんて気味が悪いよ
It's so sickening how even love, salvation, and kindness are completely baseless
ラブソングなんかか痛いのだって防衛本能だ
The aching feeling you get from some love song is a self-preservation instinct
どうでもいいか あんたのせいだ
I don't care, it's all your fault
考えたってわからないし 生きてるだけでも苦しいし
Even if I think it over, I don't understand, it hurts so much just being alive
音楽とか儲かんないし 歌詞とか適当でもいいよ
Music and all that won't sell, lyrics and such can be careless
どうでもいいんだ 間違ってないよな
I don't care, I don't think I'm wrong
間違ってないよな 間違ってないよな
I can't be wrong, I can't be wrong...
間違ってんだよ わかってるんだ
I've got it all wrong, I get it now
あんたも人間も
But all you humans are just as wrong
本当も愛も救いも優しさも人生も
I don't care about truth, love, solace, kindness, or life
それもいいんだ 正しい答えが言えないのだって防衛本能だ
Being unable to give the right answer is a self-defense instinct
どうでもいいや あんたのせいだ
I don't care, it's all your fault
僕だって信念があった 今じゃゴミみたいな想いだ
Even I once had faith in something, now it's just some garbage feeling
何度でも君を描いた 売れることこそがどうでもよかったんだ
I wrote about you over and over, whether I'd be famous was the least of my worries
本当だ 本当なんだ 昔はそうだった
It's true, it's really the truth, that's how it was back then
だから僕は音楽を辞めた
That's why I gave up on music
踊るポンポコリン
[Music]
なんでもかんでも みんな 踊りを踊っているよ
No matter what, everyone is dancing
おなぺの中から ボワっと インチキおじさん 登場
Sailing out from inside the pot, an impostor old man appears
いつだって わすれない エジソンは えらい人
I will never forget, Edison is a great person
そんなの常識 タッタタラリラ
That's common sense, tatta tararira
ピーヒャラ ピーヒャラ パッパパラパ
Piihyara piihyara pappa parapa
ピーヒャラ ピーヒャラ おへそがちらり タッタタラリラ
Piihyara piihyara, a belly button peeking out, tatta tararira
ピーヒャラ ピーヒャラ パッパパラパ
Piihyara piihyara pappa parapa
ピーヒャラ ピーヒャラ おどるポンポコリン
Piihyara piihyara odoru ponpokorin
ピーヒャラ ピ お腹がへったよ
Piihyara pi, my stomach is empty
あの子も この子も みんな いそいで 歩いているよ
This child and that child, everyone is walking in a hurry
でんしんばしらの かげから お笑い芸人 登場
From the shadow of a utility pole, a comedy entertainer appears
いつだって 迷わない キヨスクは 駅の中
Always without hesitation, Kiosk is inside the station
そんなの 有名 タッタタラリラ
That's famous, tatta tararira
ピーヒャラ ピーヒャラ パッパパラパ
Piihyara piihyara pappa parapa
ピーヒャラ ピーヒャラ ニンジンのいらない タッタタラリラ
Piihyara piihyara, don't need carrots, tatta tararira
ピーヒャラ ピーヒャラ パッパパラパ
Piihyara piihyara pappa parapa
ピーヒャラ ピーヒャラ おどるポンポコリン
Piihyara piihyara odoru ponpokorin
ピーヒャラ ピ ブタのプータロー
Piihyara pi, the lazy pig
いつだって わすれない エジソンは えらい人
I will never forget, Edison is a great person
そんなの常識 タッタタラリラ
That's common sense, tatta tararira
ピーヒャラ ピーヒャラ パッパパラパ
Piihyara piihyara pappa parapa
ピーヒャラ ピーヒャラ おへそがちらり タッタタラリラ
Piihyara piihyara, a belly button peeking out, tatta tararira
ピーヒャラ ピーヒャラ パッパパラパ
Piihyara piihyara pappa parapa
ピーヒャラ ピーヒャラ おどるポンポコリン
Piihyara piihyara odoru ponpokorin
なんでもかんでも　みんな
Anything and everything, everyone
踊りを踊っているよ
is dancing away.
おなかの中から　ボワッと
Out from inside our bellies, pop!
インチキおじさん　登場
The phony old man appears.
いつだって　忘れない
We'll never forget,
エジソンは　えらい人
Edison was a great man.
そんなの常識　タッタタラリラ
That's common sense, tatta tararira.
ピィヒャラ　ピィヒャラ　パッパパラパ
Piihyara piihyara pappa parapa,
ピィヒャラ　ピィヒャラ　おどるポンポコリン
piihyara piihyara, dancing Ponpokorin!
ピィヒャラ　ピィ　お腹がへったよ
Piihyara pii, my stomach is empty.
あの子も　この子も　みんな
That girl and this girl, everyone
いそういで歩いているよ
is hurrying along.
でんしんばしらの　かげから
From the shadow of the telephone pole,
お笑い芸人　登場
a comedian appears.
いつだって　迷わない
We'll never get lost,
キヨスクは　駅の中
KIOSK is right inside the station.
そんなの有名　タッタタラリラ
Everyone knows that, tatta tararira.
ピィヒャラ　ピィヒャラ　パッパパラパ
Piihyara piihyara pappa parapa,
piihyara piihyara pappa parapa,
ピィヒャラ　ピィヒャラ　ニンジンいらない
piihyara piihyara, no need for carrots,
タッタタラリラ
tatta tararira!
ピィヒャラ　ピィヒャラ　パッパパラパ
Piihyara piihyara pappa parapa,
ピィヒャラ　ピィヒャラ　おどるポンポコリン
piihyara piihyara, dancing Ponpokorin!
いつだって　忘れない
We'll never forget,
エジソンは　えらい人
Edison was a great man.
そんなの常識　タッタタラリラ
That's common sense, tatta tararira.
ピィヒャラ　ピィヒャラ　パッパパラパ
Piihyara piihyara pappa parapa,
ピィヒャラ　ピィヒャラ　おどるポンポコリン
piihyara piihyara, dancing Ponpokorin!
ピィヒャラ　ピィ　おなかが出たよ
Piihyara pii, my belly is sticking out!
ピィヒャラ　ピィヒャラ　パッパパラパ
Piihyara piihyara pappa parapa,
piihyara piihyara pappa parapa,
ピィヒャラ　ピィヒャラ　ニンジンいらない
piihyara piihyara, no need for carrots,
タッタタラリラ
tatta tararira!
ピィヒャラ　ピィヒャラ　パッパパラパ
Piihyara piihyara pappa parapa,
ピィヒャラ　ピィヒャラ　おどるポンポコリン
piihyara piihyara, dancing Ponpokorin!
ピィヒャラ　ピィ　おなかが出たよ
Piihyara pii, my belly is sticking out!
はーい！ありがとうございました！おどるポンポコリンでした！
Thank you very much! That was "Odoru Pompokorin"!
えーっと、絶対みんなが知ってる曲にしようと思ってさ、今日。
Um, I wanted to pick a song that absolutely everyone would know today.
これだったらさ、さすがにどの年代の人でも分かってもらえると思って選びました！
I chose this thinking that people of any generation would surely recognize it!
え、どうだった？
So, how was it?
よかった、歓声めっちゃいい感じだった！本当によかった、狙い通り！
Yay, the cheers felt amazing! I'm so glad, right as planned!
はい、ちょっとお水飲んで休憩します。
Alright, I'm gonna drink some water and take a quick break.
え、ちょっと、あの、ちょっと緊張して、コメント見る暇なかったからコメント見るぞ！
Um, I was a bit nervous and didn't have time to look at the chat, so let's check it out!
おお、のど飴舐めろ、風邪引く。よかった、お水助かる、楽しめる曲！
"Oh, suck on a throat drop, you'll catch a cold." "Glad water helps, fun song!"
この選曲は読めない。
"Nobody saw this song choice coming."
でしょ？もうね、みんなに予想外をね、今日はあの、お届けしようと思って。
Right? I wanted to deliver something unexpected to everyone today.
いい感じだったでしょ？あの、背景切り替えるタイミングも、なんかまるでモデルもっとみたいだったでしょ？間違えただけだよ！
It was great, right? And the background switch timing... felt almost like a model mode, right? I just messed up!
え、キュンとした？本当？やった、嬉しい、よかった！
Huh, did it make your heart flutter? Really? Yay, I'm so happy!
ありがとう、イエイ、見てる見てるよ、ありがとう！
Thank you, yay, I see you guys, thank you!
さあ、こっからはね、まだね、まだね、初披露の曲がありますよ、みんな！
Now, from here on, we still have songs being performed for the first time, everyone!
ちょっとね、なるべくいろんな人に、いろんな世代の人に伝わる曲にしようと思って、ちょっと練習してきて、次もね、その曲がね。
I practiced hard so that it would resonate with as many people across different generations as possible, and the next song is...
ちょっとね、次、次ちょっと緊張なんだよね、ネネ的には。ちょっと、なかなかね、難しくて覚えるのが、ちょっと大変だったけど。
Well, I'm a bit nervous about the next one. It was pretty difficult and tough to memorize,
これはもう絶対に受かる、絶対に聞いたことある！歌詞では知らなくても、絶対に聞いたことある！もうお誕生日がある日に
but this one is definitely a hit, everyone's heard it! Even if you don't know the lyrics, you've definitely heard it on your birthday,
あの、ふさわしい曲。
a fitting song for that day.
ということにしとくわ！あ、何回でもいいよ！ねえねえ、お誕生日だから何回でもね！
Let's go with that! Oh, any number of times is fine! Hey hey, since it's my birthday, as many times as you want!
ハッピーバースデーねねち！ハッピーバースデーねねち！自分おめでとう、おめでとうねね！
Happy birthday Nenechi! Happy birthday Nenechi! Congrats to myself, congrats Nene!
あ、最後まで見て！お願い、最後まで見て！よし！
Ah, watch till the end! Please, watch till the end! Okay!
じゃあ、次の曲いっちゃおうかな！じゃあ、背景をね、こっちにしたいと思います！
Well then, shall we go to the next song? Alright, I'll switch the background to this one!
よし！じゃあ、次の選曲もみんな
Okay! Now, for the next song selection, everyone,
え、よかったらね、当ててみてください！何でしょうか？もう発表しちゃうけど。
if you'd like, try guessing it! What could it be? I'm gonna announce it right away though.
え、それでは、え、4曲目、聞いてください。「Tomorrow」。
Well then, please listen to the fourth song, "Tomorrow".
涙の数だけ強くなれるよ
Each tear you shed makes you stronger,
アスファルトに咲く花のように
like a flower blooming in the asphalt.
見るものすべてにおびえないで
Don't be scared of everything you see;
明日は来るよ 君のために
tomorrow will come for you.
突然逢いたいなんて
Out of the blue, you say you want to see me...
涙の数だけ 強くなれるよ
Each tear you shed makes you stronger,
アスファルトに咲く 花のように
like a flower blooming on the asphalt.
見るものすべてに おびえないで
Don't be afraid of everything you see,
明日は来るよ 君のために
tomorrow will come for you.
突然会いたいなんて 夜更けに
Out of the blue, you wanted to see me—
何があったの
what happened in the middle of the night?
慌ててジョークにしても その笑顔が悲しい
Though you try to laugh it off as a joke, your smile is sad.
ビルの上には ほら月明かり
Up above the buildings, the moonlight shines down.
抱きしめてる 思い出とか プライドとか
If you let go of the memories and pride you're holding onto,
捨てたらまたいいことあるから
good things will happen again.
涙の数だけ 強くなれるよ
Each tear you shed makes you stronger,
アスファルトに咲く 花のように
like a flower blooming on the asphalt.
見るものすべてに おびえないで
Don't be afraid of everything you see,
明日は来るよ 君のために
tomorrow will come for you.
季節を忘れるくらい 色んなことがあるけど
So many things have happened, enough to make me forget the seasons,
二人でただ歩いている この感じが愛しい
but walking by your side like this feels so precious.
頼りにしてるだけど 時には
I lean on you, but sometimes
夢の荷物 投げ出して 泣いてもいいよ
it's okay to cast aside the burden of your dreams and cry.
寄り合うから カッコつけないで
When we're together, don't try to look tough.
涙の数だけ 強くなろうよ
Each tear you shed will make you stronger,
風に揺れている 花のように
like a flower swaying in the wind.
自分をそのまま 信じていてね
Just believe in yourself as you are,
明日は来るよ どんな時も
tomorrow will always come, no matter what.
涙の数だけ 強くなれるよ
Each tear you shed makes you stronger,
アスファルトに咲く 花のように
like a flower blooming on the asphalt.
見るものすべてに おびえないで
Don't be afraid of everything you see,
明日は来るよ 君のために
tomorrow will come for you.
涙の数だけ 強くなろうよ
Each tear you shed will make you stronger,
風に揺れている 花のように
like a flower swaying in the wind.
自分をそのまま 信じていてね
Just believe in yourself as you are,
明日は来るよ どんな時も
tomorrow will always come, no matter what.
明日は来るよ 君のために
Tomorrow will come for you.
涙の数だけ 強くなろうよ
Each tear you shed will make you stronger,
風に揺れている 花のように
like a flower swaying in the wind.
自分をそのまま 信じていてね
Just believe in yourself as you are,
明日は来るよ どんな時も
tomorrow will always come, no matter what.
明日は来るよ 君のために
Tomorrow will come for you.
涙の数だけ 強くなろうよ
Each tear you shed will make you stronger,
風に揺れている 花のように
like a flower swaying in the wind.
自分をそのまま 信じていてね
Just believe in yourself as you are,
明日は来るよ どんな時も
tomorrow will always come, no matter what.
明日は来るよ 君のために
Tomorrow will come for you.
ありがとうございました！TOMORROWでした。
Thank you very much! That was "Tomorrow".
ネネよりは上の年代の曲なんだけど、
These are songs from a generation above mine, but
この、この年代の曲たちもめちゃくちゃいい曲たちが多くて、なんか、
there are so many amazing songs from this era too.
今回ね、その選ぶにあたって、何個か迷った曲がまだあって、まあ、いつかネネ、あの披露できるようにちょっと練習をねしていきたいと思っております。
In choosing this time, there are still a few songs I hesitated on, so I'm hoping to practice them so I can perform them someday.
あ、緊張した！この曲、全然おぼんなくて、本当に難しくて、なんか
Ah, I was so nervous! I didn't know this song at all, it was really hard, and...
ああ、緊張した。今日緊張したしか言ってない。お水飲みます。
Ah, I was so nervous. I've only said I'm nervous today. I'll drink some water.
いつか聞かせるじゃ、任せな！いつかね、リクエストもね、あの、募集してますので、あの
Leave it to me to play it for you someday! We're also taking requests, so...
なんか、いい曲など、歌ってほしい曲とかあったら、あの、ネネにわかるように書いといでください！
if there are good songs or songs you want me to sing, please write them so Nene can understand!
いや、あるよ！まだあるよ、今日はね、初発表の曲がまだあります。
No, there are more! There are still more songs being announced for the first time today.
ねえ、緊張するな。ちょっとね。
Man, I'm so nervous. A bit.
次は、あの、おねがいマッスルの時に、あの、ネネのね、あのセルフ愛のてがすごく、すごく好評で嬉しかったから、今回もちょっとセルフ愛のてを入れて、1曲歌ってみたいと思っております！
Next, when I did "Onegai Muscle", Nene's "self-love hand" was really well-received and made me happy, so this time too, I'd like to put in the "self-love hand" and sing a song!
ース！というわけで次の曲いきましょう！
Yes! So let's move on to the next song!
お誕生日の、お誕生日ガールのネネが楽しく歌う楽しい曲、移動しよう！
A fun song sung cheerfully by the birthday girl, Nene! Let's move!
ぱい！
Boom!
単純な言葉重ねていく
Repeating simple words over and over,
もっと心は素直で
wanting my heart to be more honest.
なんでもないような その笑顔が 明日を照らす光に
That smile, as if it was nothing special, becomes light for tomorrow.
ずっと気づいていたんだって この手に抱えていたんだって
I've always noticed it, I've always held it in these hands.
弾けた声に流した答えが
The answer I shed into my bursting voice
今 そっと きっと 願い込めて
now softly and surely holds a wish.
ずっと まわる まわる 夢の中で
Always, spinning and spinning in my dreams,
繰り返し 君 と 踊った
I danced with you over and over.
揺れる 景色 道 は 続く
Swaying scenery, the road continues,
通り過ぎる 風 に ふ かれ
blown by the passing wind.
何度も 越え て 行ける から
Because I can cross over time and time again,
境界線 雲 かき分け 手 を 伸ばし た
I parted the clouds and reached out my hand.
涙 は 今 浮かぶ 空 に
Entrusting my tears to the floating sky,
預け て 走り出す の
I start to run.
並ん で 見つめ た
Side by side,
輝く 光 を 手 に
holding the shining light in my hands.
問題 は いつも 自分 次第
The problem is always up to myself,
さあ 未来 を 選ん で
come, choose the future.
こんがらがっ た 糸 ほど い たら
If I untangle the tangled threads,
思いのまま 進 も う
I'll move forward just as I feel.
毎日 冒険 なん だって
Every day is an adventure,
奇跡 は 無限大 なん だって
miracles are infinite.
高鳴る 想い 羅針盤 の ような
My throbbing feelings, like a compass,
今 そっと きっと 導 い て く
will guide me softly and surely now.
そうだ！めぐる めぐる 波 に 乗っかっ て 風 まかせ 君 と 笑っ た
That's right! Riding the spinning waves, leaving it to the wind, I laughed with you.
予想 外 は 想定内
The unexpected is within expectations,
間違い や 失敗 も 楽しん で
enjoying mistakes and failures as well.
一歩 踏み出し たら 見え た 可能性
Stepping forward, possibilities came into view,
行き止まり の 壁 壊し て
breaking down the wall of a dead end.
まだ 知ら ない 世界 君 と 一緒 なら
If I'm with you in a world I don't know yet,
怖く ない よ
I'm not afraid.
わくわく し て いる 今 が 一番 大好き
The present moment, when I'm excited, is what I love most.
ゆっくり 焦らない 自分 の ペース で 行こう
Slowly, don't rush, let's go at our own pace.
どんな大変な事が起きたって
No matter what difficult things happen,
君の足のその下には
right beneath your feet,
とてもとても丈夫な「ばね」が
there's an extremely sturdy "spring"
ついてんだぜ (知ってた?)
attached to you! (Did you know?)
おしつぶされそうな そんなときだって
Even in times when you feel crushed,
ぐっ!とひざっ小僧に勇気をため
gather courage in your knees with a "Guts!",
「いまだ!スタンバイ!OK!」その時を待つのさ
and wait for the moment: "Now! Standby! OK!"
びゅ〜ら〜り〜ら〜 風が君を呼んでいるよ
Swish-swoosh, the wind is calling you.
ボヨヨヨ〜ンと空へ 飛びあがってみよう
Bo-yo-yo-ing, let's leap up into the sky!
ほら あの雲まで 手がとどきそう
Look, we can almost reach those clouds.
ボヨヨヨ〜ンと 高く 飛び越えてゆこう
Bo-yo-yo-ing, let's leap high across them!
虹のふもとで 笑顔で待ってる君がいる
At the foot of the rainbow, you're waiting with a smile.
雲の切れ間を伸ばした
Stretching through the breaks in the clouds,
涙は今 浮かぶ空に預けて
leave your tears to the floating sky right now.
走り出すの ならんで見つけた
Start running, side by side, we found
輝く光を 手に
a shining light in our hands,
わくわくしている
and we're so excited!
今が一番大好き
Right now is what I love the most!
続いて、そのまま次の曲 お聴きください。
Next, please enjoy our next song just as it is.
さよならメモリーズ
Sayonara Memories.
桜が咲くよ
The cherry blossoms are blooming
見慣れたいつもの坂道に
on the familiar, usual hill road.
ああ 別れを
Ah, saying goodbye—
泣いて笑ったあのの日々が
those days we laughed and cried
なんだか昨日のことのように
feel somehow like just yesterday.
この道はそう 未来へ続く道
This road, yes, is a road leading to the future,
そんな気がしたの
or so it felt to me.
3月でね、卒業シーズンだから！ぜひ卒業ソングはあたごもとまでまって選びました！聴いててね！
Since March is graduation season! I specifically chose graduation songs for you! Listen closely!
泣いて笑った
Those days we laughed and cried
あの日々
together...
なんだか昨日のことのように
feel somehow like just yesterday.
この道はそう 未来へ続く道
This road, yes, is a road leading to the future,
そんな気がしたの
or so it felt to me.
例年より早い開花予想を キミは嬉しがってた
You were so happy about the cherry blossoms blooming earlier than usual.
私は笑って「そうだね」って言った
I smiled and said, "That's right."
あと少ししたらもう ここには戻れないのに
Even though in just a little while we won't be able to return here,
言葉じゃうまく言えない想いを キミに打ち明けだとしたらなんて
if I were to confess the feelings I can't put into words...
伝えよう 最初で最後に
I'll convey them, for the first and last time.
いつか一緒に帰った道は 私にとって特別な思い出
The road we once walked home together is a special memory to me.
忘れないよ さよならメモリーズ
I won't forget it. Goodbye, memories.
春が来たら それぞれの道を行こう
When spring comes, let's walk our separate paths,
また会える日を願って
hoping for the day we can meet again.
さよなら 小さくつぶやいた
I whispered a quiet "Goodbye."
空はあの日と変わらず 青くて
The sky was just as blue as that day,
だから ちょっと泣けた
so I cried a little.
また会える日を
Hoping for the day we can meet again,
願って
praying...
さよなら 小さくつぶやいた
I whispered a quiet "Goodbye."
空はあの日と
The sky, just like that day,
変わらず
remained unchanged
青くて
and blue,
だから ちょっと泣けた
so I cried a little.
わざと遠回りしたの
I took a detour on purpose,
少しでも長く キミの隣にいたくて
wanting to be by your side just a little longer.
私はおどけて 「まちがえた」って言った
I acted playful and said, "I took a wrong turn."
キミは笑う その顔がまぶしくて目をそらした
You smiled, and that face was so dazzling I averted my eyes.
言葉じゃうまく言えない想いを 胸に抱いてこの道を歩いた
Holding feelings I couldn't put into words in my chest, I walked this road
覚えてる あの時キミは 私の名前を呼んでくれた
and remember—back then, you called out my name.
桜が咲くよ 見慣れたいつもの坂道に ああ 別れを
Cherry blossoms bloom on the familiar hill path... Ah, saying goodbye.
泣いて笑ったあの日々なんだか昨日のことのように
Those days of crying and laughing feel just like yesterday.
この道はそう 未来へ続く道 そんな気がしたのか
This road, yes, feels like a path leading to the future.
例年より早い開花予想を君は喜んでいた
You were so happy the cherry blossoms bloomed earlier than usual.
私は笑って「そうだね」って言った
I just smiled and said, "That's right."
あと少ししたらもう ここには戻れないのに
Even though soon we won't be able to return here anymore.
言葉じゃうまく言えない想いを君に打ち明けるとしたらなんて伝えよう
If I were to finally confess these words I can't put well...
いつか一緒に帰った道は私にとって特別な思い出
The path we walked home together is such a special memory.
忘れないよ さよならメモリーズ
I won't forget it, goodbye memories.
春が来たら それぞれの道を また会える日を願って
When spring comes, each to our own path, wishing to meet again.
さよなら 小さくつぶやいた
I whispered a small "goodbye."
空はあの日と変わらず青くて だからちょっと泣けた
The sky was blue just like that day, so I cried a little.
わざと遠回りしたの 少しでも長く君のそばにいたくて
I took a detour on purpose, wanting to be by your side longer.
私はおどけて「まちがえた」って言った
I acted playfully and said, "I made a mistake."
君は笑う その顔が眩しくて目をそらした
You smiled, and that face was so dazzling I looked away.
言葉じゃうまく言えない想いを胸に抱いてこの道を歩いた
Holding feelings I can't express in my chest, I walked this road.
覚えてるあの時君は 私の名前を呼んでくれた 二人夕暮れの帰り道で
I remember you calling my name on our way home in the twilight.
忘れないよ さよならメモリーズ 出会えたこと感謝してる
I won't forget, goodbye memories. I'm so grateful we met.
初めて見た満開の桜 あれからどれくらい 変われなんだろう
The first full-bloom cherry blossoms... how much have I changed since?
一目見た時に思ったんだ この人のこと好きになりそうって
The moment I first saw you, I thought I'd fall in love with you.
なんでか なんでかわかんないよ
I wonder why? I just don't know why.
それからの毎日はとても楽しくて だけど同じくらいに 辛かったんだ
Every day after was so fun, but at the same time just as painful.
ごめんね なんかうまく言えないよ だから私君となんて言うか
I'm sorry, I can't say it right. That's why, you and I...
今のまま さよならしたくないの
I don't want to say goodbye just like this.
友達のままでじゃ もう嫌なの
I don't want to stay just friends anymore.
言おうと思ってた 私君の 君のことずっと ずっと 前から 好きでした ああ やっと言えた
I've loved you for so long. Ah, I finally said it.
ありがとうございました！
Thank you very much!
アドレナリンとさよならメモリーズ 2曲続けてお聞きいただきましたーー！
You listened to Adrenaline and Sayonara Memories back to back!
え、どうだった？
How was it?
ちょっとさよならメモリーズは結構 結構結構練習したから いい感じにみんなの耳に聴こえてたらいいなと思っております
I practiced Sayonara Memories quite a lot, so I hope it sounded nice.
やばすぎ！やばすぎか！やばすぎ嬉しいな ありがとう！
So amazing! So amazing! I'm so happy, thank you!
えっとというわけで ここからは まだまだ歌ってまいりたいのですが
Well then, from here on, I'd like to keep singing more, but...
その前にねねから 10ダハピの前にお知らせがあります！
Before that, I have an announcement from Nene before the 100k subscriber milestone!
ちょっとお知らせ そしてもろていかな！
An announcement... and Monoteyakana!
えっとというわけでちょっと明るいステージ このままでいっかな？
Well then, let's go with this bright stage, is this fine?
もうねねの概要欄を見て ちょっとね あの冊ッチみたいな人もいるかもしれないのですが
You might have checked Nene's description and seen a booklet,
ねねち初の公式ソログッズでまーーす！ でででででん！ドン！
Nenechi's first official solo goods are coming out! Ta-da-da-da-dam! Bam!
ももすずねね 誕生日記念 2021 イェーーイ！
Momosuzu Nene Birthday Anniversary 2021! Yay!
内容は ボイスのボイスとグッズ あと西沢5ミリ先生描き下ろしのアクリルパネルと
The contents include voice items, goods, and an acrylic panel illustrated by Nishizawa 5-mili...
じゃあ見て見て！ あー かわいい！
Now look, look! Ah, so cute!
じっくりねねの直筆文字のアクリルパネル、
An acrylic panel featuring Nene's handwritten text up close,
そして、えー、えっとね、グッズの方が
and, um, let's see, as for the goods,
ドン！「ねねプロ」社員ピンバッチ＆「ねねプロ」社員カードが
ta-da! The "Nene Pro" Employee Pin Badge & Card
出ます！
are coming out!
社員ピンバッチ見て！これ、あの、「ねねプロ」アクションの
Look at the pin badge! This is the official logo of Nene Pro Action,
あの公式ロゴが出来上がりました！「ね」「ね」って書いてあるやつと、
that's been completed! The one with "Ne Ne" written on it,
社員カードはなんと！ハズバンズナンバー入り！シリアルナンバーが入ります！
and the employee card has—guess what! Husbands number included with a serial number!
みんなね、今まで勝手にナンバー乗ってたけど、とうとう、あの公式的に、あの番号が配られることになりました！
Everyone, up until now you've had numbers assigned on your own, but finally, officially, you're getting assigned numbers!
イェーイ！イェーイ！
Yay! Yay!
そう、社員証なんだけど、あのハズバンズ、ハズバンズナンバーって書いてあるんだよね。
Right, it's an employee ID, and it says "Husbands, Husbands Number" on it.
ちょっとアップで見てほしい。あ、ちょっと待って、これじゃねえ、これじゃねえ。
I want you to see it close up. Ah, wait, not this, not this.
えーっとこっち。よいしょ。
Um, this one. Here we go.
ほら、どどどどどど！ほら、見て！ハズバンズナンバー入ります！
Look, ta-da-da-da-da! Look, see? The husband's number will be included!
そして、なんと！裏面は、あ、ねねが提出物の嵐に遭っていた時何を書いていたのかと言うと、
And amazingly, on the back—when Nene was swarmed with assignments, what was she writing, you ask?
社員カードの、いや、社員証の裏面にはなんとねねの、えー、オリジナルの描き下ろしのイラストとメッセージ！
On the back of the employee card—well, employee ID—there is Nene's original newly drawn illustration and message!
そしてね、この裏面のデザインね、なんとねねがしました！いー！
And you know, Nene designed this back side herself! Yay!
名前書くところ書いたので、みんなにそれぞれの名前を書いて持ち歩いてほしい！いェーイ！
Since there's a place to write your name, I want everyone to write their own name and carry it around! Yay!
で、そんでもって、そんでもって、えー、全部セットっていうのがございまして、全部全部にすると、
And then, um, there is a "complete set", and if you get the all-in-one set,
はい、グッズ＆ボイス全部セットの特典は、なんとねねの直筆サイン入り「西沢5ミリ先生描き下ろしイラストポストカード」＋特典ボイス！
yes, the perk for the goods & voice complete set is, amazingly, Nene's hand-signed postcard illustrated by Nishizawa 5-miri-sensei + bonus voice!
見て、ポストカードの、ポストカードのこれ見て見て見て見て！
Look, look at this postcard, look, look, look, look!
ほら、みんなの腕が生えてるー！
Look, everyone's arms are growing out of it!
ええ！？
Eh?!
いー！ねね、なでなでされてるんだけど！
Yay! Nene is getting her head patted!
ねね、なぜなんでされてるんだけど、ライブ前のねねをね、応援、応援してくれているみんなをね、あの、あの、イメージでそんな感じにしていただきました！
Nene is getting head-patted, and I imagined everyone cheering on Nene before her live performance, and that's the kind of vibe I went with!
えー、みんなね、ここにコラージュして自分の、自分の写真撮って自分でコラージュしてさ、まるで自分がなでなでしてるみたいな感じでやってほしい！
Everyone, collage yourselves into this, take your own photo, collage it yourself, and do it like you're the one patting her head!
さあ、えー、グッズの紹介をしたところで、カートオープンが45分になります！あと2分で、えー、カートオープンで販売開始が21時となりますので、えー、21時まではね、ねねの配信見るでしょ？みんな、見て見て見てってね。
Now, having introduced the goods, the cart opens at :45! In 2 minutes, sales start at 21:00, so until 21:00 you'll watch Nene's stream, right everyone? Look, look, look, right?
はい。えー、これスミッコ置いとこっかな。スミッコ置いとこっかな。
Yes. Um, I'll put this in the corner. I'll put this in the corner.
どーん！すごいとこ！
Ta-da! What a place!
はい、というわけで、えー、このテンションぶち上げのところで、次も初披露の曲聴いてもらいたいと思います。
Yes, so with that tension hyped all the way up, I'd like you to listen to another song being performed for the first time.
それでは、聴いてください。春擬き。
Without further ado, please listen. Harumodoki.
探しに行くんだ そこへ
I'm going to search for it, right there
空欄を埋め 完成した定規
Filling in the blanks, a completed ruler
正しい筈なのに
Even though it should be right,
はらりひらり からまわる
Spinning around, fluttering away
未来は歪で
The future is distorted
僅かな亀裂から いくらでも綻んで
From a slight crack, fraying endlessly
理想から逸れていくんだ
Straying away from the ideal
ぬるま湯が すっと冷めていく音がしてた
I heard the lukewarm water quietly cooling down
道を変えるのなら 今なんだ
If I'm going to change my path, now is the time
こんなレプリカは いらない
I don't need a replica like this
本物と呼べるものだけでいい
I only want what can be called the real thing
探しに行くんだ そこへ
I'm going to search for it, right there
「でもそれは よく出来たフェアリーテイルみたい。」
"But that sounds like a well-made fairytale."
応えの消えた 空欄を見つめる
Gazing at the blank space where the answer disappeared
埋めた筈なのに どうしても 解らない
Even though I filled it in, I still don't understand
はい！はい！はい！はい！
Hai! Hai! Hai! Hai!
答えの消えた
The answer vanished
クルマを見つめる
as I gaze at the car.
褒めたはずなのに
Even though I should have praised it,
どうしてもわからない
I just don't understand why.
綺麗な花は 大事に育てても
Even if you carefully raise a beautiful flower,
遠慮ない速度で 簡単に関みにじられた
it gets ruthlessly and easily trampled.
降り積もる白に
Over the piling white snow,
小さな目 覆われてく
small buds are covered up.
遠い 遠い春は
A distant, distant spring
雪の知った 見えないものは どうしても
and the invisible things known to the snow, no matter what,
記憶から薄れてしまうんだ 探しに行く
fade away from my memory. Even the place I'm going to search for
場所さえも 見失う僕たちは
is lost, and we walk on
気づかず目を踏む
without even noticing.
想い出を頼りに作ってた 花はすぐ枯れた
The flowers I made relying on memories withered right away.
足元には 気づかずに
Without even noticing what's at my feet...
本物と呼べる 場所を
The place we can call the real thing—
探しに行くのは きっと
searching for it is surely
今なんだ こんなレプリカはいらない
happening now. I don't need any replica like this.
本物と呼べるものだけでいい
I only want things that can be called the real thing.
探しに行くから 君を
I'm going to search for you,
ありがとう小さめ 見つけてくれたこと
thank you, little bud, for finding me.
君は呟いた
You whispered.
さて皆様！場所移動してねね！ぴょーん！
Now everyone! Moving locations, Nene! Pyon!
ここからは ねねの 重大発表の時間です！イェーイ！
From here on is Nene's major announcement time! Yay!
え、なんとなんと え、ここからは この曲は切り抜き禁止です！
Um, what- what, um, from here on, clips of this song are prohibited!
え、なんでなんで？
Eh, why, why?!
ああ、お水も飲んで整えさせて
Ah, let me drink some water and catch my breath.
みんながね、重大発表ね、すごい楽しみにしてくれてて いろんなね、予想をね、Twitterでしてくれたりしてるの見て
Everyone was looking forward to the major announcement so much, and seeing you all making various guesses on Twitter,
ねねもね、なんか、もうね、内容知ってるのに、なんかワクワクしちゃってて すごい、今から発表できるのが、とってもとってもとってもとってもとっても楽しみ！
even though Nene already knew what it was, I got so excited, and I'm super, super, super, super, super excited to announce it right now!
そう、お水飲まなきゃ
Right, I gotta drink water.
50万人おめでとう！え、50万人いったの？
Congrats on 500k! Eh, we hit 500k?!
は、ハッピーバースデーお誕生日記念日かぶった！
Ha, happy birthday and anniversary overlapped!
え、嬉しすぎ、無理無理無理！どうしよう、テンション爆上げで重大発表できそう！
Eh, too happy, impossible impossible! What should I do, my hype is through the roof, I can make the major announcement!
それでは、ねねからの今日の重大発表
Well then, today's major announcement from Nene...
発表します！さあ、3、2、1、ドン！
I'll announce it! 3, 2, 1, boom!
桃鈴ねね 1stシングル「ねねねねねねね！大爆走」配信開始！オリジナル曲発表！イェーイ！
Momosuzu Nene's 1st single "Nenene Nenene Nenene! Daibakusou" releasing! Original song announcement! Yay!
なんと、作詞・作曲・編曲 ねねの大好きな...
And what's more, lyrics, composition, and arrangement by Nene's favorite...
ヒゲドライバーさんにお願いしましたー！
I asked Hige Driver-san!
なんと！今日の日付が変わった、
And guess what! Today—well, the date changed,
3月3日0時から配信開始になります！
and it will start streaming from midnight on March 3rd!
なんとジャケットはねねの描き下ろし！
And the jacket art is completely drawn by Nene!
頑張って描いた！ロゴもねねが作ったー！
I worked so hard drawing it! Nene even made the logo!
え、なんで切り抜き禁止かと言うと、
Um, the reason why making clips is prohibited is because
え、今からここで初発表、生初出しさせてもらうんですけど、
um, I'm going to premiere it right here live for the first time, but
まだMVがね、えー完成してなくて、
the music video isn't finished yet, um,
えー、それまでは切り抜きを禁止にしてMVを待ってもらいたい、
um, until then I'd like to prohibit clips and have everyone wait for the MV,
そんな意志で、今回切り抜き禁止にさせていただきました。
so I decided to prohibit clip-making this time.
こんなのまで作っちゃってね、フォトショップ触れるようになってからこんなのまで作っちゃってねね
I even made something like this! Ever since I learned to use Photoshop, I made this too.
えーどんな曲だと思う？どんな曲だと思う？
Um, what kind of song do you think it is? What kind of song do you think?
なんと、なんとなんとなんと、えーちょっと聞いてほしい
Guess what, guess what, um... I want you to listen.
あいの手が入ってるんだけど、あいのてはね、ごきげんのみんなに応援してもらいました！
There are call-and-response parts, and I had everyone in a good mood cheer me on!
みんなありがとう！すごいね、あのタイトなスケジュールだったんだけど
Thank you everyone! It was a really tight schedule, but
みんなね、もう一言返事で「いいよ」って言ってくれて、あのすごいすごい良い曲になりました。
everyone replied with just a word saying 'Sure', and it became such an amazing song.
もう嬉しすぎ！もうずっとね準備してて
I'm so happy! I've been preparing for this all along,
もう発表、発表がね、あの楽しみで楽しみで、もうしょうがなくって
and I was just so overwhelmingly excited and looking forward to the announcement,
もう今日ここで、あの歌えるのがもう本当にね、楽しみ！
that I'm just genuinely so excited to be able to sing it right here today!
ちょっともうさ、なんか、なんか歓声上がっちゃってさ、泣きそうなんだけどさ、ちょっと、あのなるべくね、あのCD音源に近く歌えるように頑張りますので
I'm getting so emotional and about to cry, but I'll do my best to sing as close to the CD sound source as possible,
えーと曲をね、ぜひ買ってほしいんだけど、まあ人にはいろいろそれぞれ事情があるからもし買えないよって人はねねのこの枠の、えーここで聞、聞いてほしい
um, I'd really love for you to buy the song, but people have different circumstances, so if you can't buy it, I want you to listen to it right here in Nene's stream,
いっぱい覚えて、ほしい！みんなで歌ってほしい！でも、ごきげんのみんなに聴いてもらったら
learn it a lot, and sing it together! But once everyone in the chat listens to it,
あのすっごい耳に残るって言ってもらえたからみんなね、耳にも残ってもらえるように頑張って頑張って今から歌いたいと
they told me it really stays in their ears, so I'm going to work hard so it stays in everyone's ears too as I sing it now.
思います。はあ、緊張、緊張する。
Haa, I'm so nervous.
そう、あのね、あの、あのみんなが曲を買ってくれたお金はねねが次のオリジナル曲作るための、費用に済ますので
Right, um, the money from everyone buying the song will be used by Nene as funds to create her next original song,
ねねが今後もアイドル目指して、あの活動を続けていけるようによかったら曲は買ってほしいなっていうねねからのお願いですよろしくお願いします！
so that Nene can continue aiming to be an idol and keep active, I kindly ask that you please buy the song if you can. Thank you very much!
というわけで歌っていきましょうか！
With that said, let's start singing!
ねねねねねねねね、大爆走！
Nenenenenenenene, Daibakusou!
あ、あせとりにきちゃった！
Ah, I started sweating!
hhaa, 緊張する！
Haa, I'm so nervous!
それでは聴いてください。
Now then, please listen.
ねねの初のオリジナル曲。
Nene's very first original song.
ななななな「な」じゃなくて
Nana nana, it's not "na"
ににににに「に」じゃなくて
Nini nini, it's not "ni"
ぬぬぬぬぬ「ぬ」じゃなくて
Nunu nunu, it's not "nu"
ののののの「の」じゃなくて…
No nonono, it's not "no"...
……「ね」！ (ねね！)
…Ooh, ne! (Nene!)
ヨイショ ヨイショ ヨイショ ヨイショ！
Yoisho, yoisho, yoisho, yoisho!
(ねね！)
(Nene!)
(ヨイショ ヨイショ ヨイショ ヨイショ！)
Yoisho, yoisho, yoisho, yoisho!
こんねね～！
Konnene~!
ホロライブ 5期生 オレンジ担当
Hololive 5th generation's orange representative
桃鈴ねね です！ (ねねち！)
Momosuzu Nene! (Nenechi!)
異世界から来ました
I came from another world,
アイドル志望の
aspiring to be an idol,
新人vtuber (何だって！？)
a rookie VTuber! (What!?)
まあ、とにかく明るくいきましょう！
Well, anyway let's stay cheerful and go!
ちょっとくらい緊張したって、
Even if I get a little nervous,
滑ったって
or slip up,
「うおー！」って感じ でさ (うおー！)
I'll shout "Ohh!" like that (Ohh!)
「どりゃあ！」ってやっていこう (どりゃあ！)
and keep going with "Toryaa!" (Toryaa!)
あきらめの悪さは長所 だよね？
Being bad at giving up is a strong point, right?
ねねねねねねねねねね (ね！)
Ne nenene nenene nenene! (Ne!)
「はぁ～ん」なこともあるけど
Sometimes things make me go "Haa-an"
悔しいこともあるけど大丈夫！
and sometimes things are frustrating, but I'll be alright!
今日もしっかり、おめかしして
Today too, I'll dress up nicely,
いつかはきっと「すーぱーねねちー！」
and someday I'll surely be "Super Nenechi!"
ついてきてね
Come along with me!
ねねねねねねね ねねねねねね
Ne nenene nenene ne nenene nenene
ねねねねねねねね (ねね！)
Ne nenene nenene nenene! (Nene!)
って、全力で行こう！
And go at full power!
そんで全開で行こう！
Yep, let's go at full throttle!
思い切りやれば何とかなるよ
If I give it my all, it'll work out somehow!
ポンコツだっていい (ヨイショ！)
Even if I'm clumsy it's good! (Yoisho!)
誤字ったっていい (ヨイショ！)
Even if I make a typo it's good! (Yoisho!)
な な な な な 「 な 」 じゃなくて
Not na-na-na-na-na, it's "ne"!
に に に に に 「 に 」 じゃなくて
Not ni-ni-ni-ni-ni, it's "ne"!
ぬ ぬ ぬ ぬ ぬ 「 ぬ 」 じゃなくて
Not nu-nu-nu-nu-nu, it's "ne"!
の の の の の 「 の 」 じゃなくて
Not no-no-no-no-no, it's "ne"!
…… 「 ね 」 ！ （ ねね ！ ） （ ヨイショ ヨイショ ヨイショ ヨイショ ！ ）
Nene! (Yoisho, yoisho, yoisho, yoisho!)
（ ねね ！ ） （ ヨイショ ヨイショ ヨイショ ヨイショ ！ ）
こんねね ～ ！ （ こんねね ～ ！ ）
Konnene~! (Konnene~!)
ホロライブ 5 期生 オレンジ 担当 桃鈴ねね です ！ （ ねね ち ～ ！ ）
I'm Hololive 5th Gen's orange representative, Momosuzu Nene! (Nenechi~!)
異世界 から 来 ま した アイドル 志望 の 新人 ｖｔｕ ｂｅｒ （ 何 だって ？！ ） まぁ 、 とにかく 明るく いき ましょ ちょっ とくらい 緊張 し たって 、 滑っ た って 「 うおー ！ 」 って 感じ で さ （ うおー ！ ） 「 どりゃあ ！ 」 って やっ て いこ う （ どりゃあ ！ ） あきらめ の 悪さ は 長所 だ よ ね ？ ねねねねねねねねね （ ね ！ ） ねねねねねねねねね （ ね ！ ）
Coming from another world, dreaming of being an idol!
「 はぁ ～ ん 」 な こと も ある けど
"Haa an" moments happen sometimes,
悔しい こと も ある けど 大丈夫 ！
and things get tough, but it'll be alright!
今日 も しっかり 、 おめかし し て いつか は きっと 「 すーぱーねね ち ！」 ついて き て ね ねねねねねねね ねねねねねねねね ねねねねねねねね （ ねね ！ ） ねねねねねね （ ね ！ ） ねねねね （ ね ！ ） ねねねねねね （ ねね ！ ）
Today I'll dress up nicely and do my best, and someday I'll be super nenechi!
って 、 全力 で いこう ！
Let's go with all our power!
そん で 全開 で いこう ！ 思い切り やれ ば なんとか なる よ
Full throttle! If I just go for it, things will work out!
ポンコツ だって いい （ ヨイショ ！ ） 誤字 だっ て いい （ ヨイショ ！ ）
Clumsy is okay! (Yoisho!) Typos are okay! (Yoisho!)
ただ 駆け抜け て いこ う ね
Let's just keep running through!
ね ！ ね ！ ね ！ ね ！ 大爆走
It's a nene-nene-nene sprint!
（ ねね ！ ） （ ヨイショ ヨイショ ヨイショ ヨイショ ！ ）
Nene! (Yoisho, yoisho, yoisho, yoisho!)
野菜 ジュース と 炭酸 と お菓子 、 そろえ て 準備 ｏｋ ！
Veggie juice, fizzy drinks, and sweets—ready to go!
でも 朝 は 苦手 （ だ ね ！） 夜 も 苦手 （ だ ね ！）
Morning is tough! (That's right!) Night is tough! (That's right!)
やっぱり 睡眠 って 、 大事 だ よ ね ？
Sleep really is important, huh?
ねねねねねねねねねね （ ね ！ ）
Ne-ne-ne-ne-ne-ne-ne-ne-ne-ne! (Ne!)
たくさん の 人 に 、 愛さ れ たい ！ ちゅちゅちゅ （ ちゅちゅちゅ ）
I wanna be loved by lots of people! Chu-chu-chu! (Chu-chu-chu!)
大好き な みんな に 、 愛さ れ たい ！ ちゅちゅちゅ （ ちゅちゅちゅ ）
I wanna be loved by my beloved fans! Chu-chu-chu! (Chu-chu-chu!)
そしたら なる ん だ 「 はいぱーねね ち ！ 」
And then I'll become hyper nenechi!
やっちゃっ て ねねねねねねね ねねねねねねね ねねねねねねねね （ ねね ！ ）
Let's go for it, ne-ne-ne-ne-ne...
って 、 全力 で いこう ！
Let's go with all our power!
そん で 全開 で いこう ！ 歌 は 誰 に も 負け たく ない ん だ
Full throttle! I don't wanna lose to anyone at singing!
大きな 声 で （ ヨイショ ！ ） あ 、 その 前 に （ ヨイショ ！ ） ちょっと トイレ 行っ て くる ね ～
A big shout out—wait, let me go to the restroom real quick!
( restroom time ! ! ! )
(Restroom time!!!)
（ ねね ！ ） （ ヨイショ ヨイショ ヨイショ ヨイショ ！ ）
Nene! (Yoisho, yoisho, yoisho, yoisho!)
ただいま ～ ！
(I'm back~!)
それじゃあ 、 また ねね ～ ！ ばいば ～ い
And with that, mata nene~! Bye-bye!